Privacy statement
=================

Information about you: how we use it and with whom we share it
--------------------------------------------------------------

The information you provide will be used by the University of California Curation Center (UC3) to offer you access to and personalization of the DMP Tool service.

The University of California Curation Center (UC3) processes the personal data of DMP Tool users in order to deliver and improve the DMP Tool service in a customized manner and to ensure each user receives relevant information.

The processing of your personal data by the University of California Curation Center (UC3) is necessary for pursuing the following legitimate interests:

* To provide access to the DMP Tool service and personalization of your user experience e.g. provision of relevant templates and guidance for your organization.
* To keep you up to date with news about DMP Tool such as new features or improvements, or changes to our Privacy Policy.
* For network and information security purposes.

We will hold the personal data you provided us for as long as you continue using the DMP Tool service. Your personal data can be removed from this service upon request to the DMP Tool team within a period of 30 days.

If you have any questions, please contact the DMP Tool team at: [dmptool@ucop.edu](mailto:dmptool@ucop.edu)

* * *

Revisions
---------

This statement was last revised on May 21st, 2018 and may be revised at any time with prior notice.

#### Quick links

#### External links

DMP Tool is a service of the California Digital Library, a division of the University of California Office of the President. Version: v5.31  
© 2024 The Regents of the University of California
